smitegame.com 2019-10-24

# 

                                     Hi-Rez Studios® Privacy Policy
                                          Last updated on July 12, 2018.
THIS PRIVACY POLICY (the “Privacy Policy”) sets forth certain terms and conditions pursuant to which Hi-
Rez Studios, Inc. (“Hi-Rez,” “we,” or “us”) may collect, store, and use certain information and data
concerning or provided by you or authorized users of your Account with Hi-Rez (collectively, “you” or
“your”) in connection with your access or use of the Site (as defined below) or any Hi-Rez game(s) or
subscription service(s) offered through the Site (the “Service”). This Privacy Policy also applies to
information or data that may be collected by Hi-Rez offline as described in this Privacy Policy below. This
Privacy Policy applies to your use of any videogame developed and/or published by Hi-Rez, and the
following websites operated by Hi-Rez and any such other websites established by Hi-Rez or its
subsidiaries from time to time which reference this Privacy Policy, including without limitation (collectively,
the “Site”):
     ●   Hi-Rez Studios®: <http://www.hirez.com>;< http://www.hirezstudios.com>;<
         http://game.hirezstudios.com>;< http://account.hirezstudios.com>
     ●   Global Agenda®: < http://www.globalagendagame.com>, http://www.globalassault.com,
         <http://www.globalassaultgame.com>
     ●   Tribes Universe™: < http://www.tribesuniverse.com>
     ●   Tribes: Ascend®: < http://www.tribesascend.com>
     ●   SMITE®: <http://www.smitegame.com>; <http://esports.smitegame.com>
     ●   Paladins®: <http://www.paladins.com>
     ●   Paladins Strike™: <http://www.paladinsstrike.com>
     ●   Hand of the Gods™: <http://www.handofthegods.com>
     ●   Jetpack Fighter®: <http://www.jetpackfighter.com>
     ●   SMITE Tactics™: <http://www.smitetactics.com>
     ●   GameVid Expo™: <http://www.gamevidexpo.com>
     ●   Bot Smashers®: <http://www.botsmashers.com>
     ●   Realm Royale™: <http://www.realmroyale.com>
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of Hi-Rez’s Terms of Service and Use Agreement.
NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME, SO PLEASE CHECK BACK
REGULARLY TO STAY INFORMED OF ANY CHANGES. MATERIAL CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY
POLICY MAY BE POSTED ON THE SITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE OR THE SERVICE,
OR ACCESSING YOUR ACCOUNT, FOLLOWING ANY SUCH CHANGES, CONSTITUTES AND
SIGNIFIES YOUR FULL ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES.
                                  NOTE TO PARENTS AND GUARDIANS
Hi-Rez does not permit access to the Site or Services by children under the age of 13. If your child is under
13 and you believe they are accessing the Site and Services, please contact us at
privacy@hirezstudios.com. Children over the age of 13 and under the age of eighteen must have their parent
or guardian review this Privacy Policy. For more information, we encourage you to review our Parent
Information page, available at <http://www.hirezstudios.com/parents>.
Consent
BY USING THIS SITE, OR ANY OF OUR SERVICES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO THIS
PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE
SITE OR ANY OTHER HI-REZ SERVICES. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES IN AND TO
THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME. PLEASE CHECK THE PRIVACY POLICY EACH TIME YOU USE
ANY OF OUR SITES OR SERVICES TO ENSURE YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY CHANGES IN OUR
PRIVACY PRACTICES. THE PRIVACY POLICY WILL INDICATE THE DATE IT WAS LAST UPDATED.

ALSO, WE MAY NOTIFY YOU VIA E-MAIL OF RELEVANT CHANGES, FOR EXAMPLE IF THERE IS A
SUBSTANTIVE CHANGE IN THE WAY THAT WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE MAY
NOTIFY YOU VIA E-MAIL. IF YOU CHOOSE TO OPT-OUT OF OUR CHANGED PRACTICE, OUR E-
MAIL WILL CONTAIN INSTRUCTIONS ON HOW TO OPT-OUT, OR YOU MAY CONTACT OUR
SUPPORT DESK
AT <http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/> OR
EMAIL privacy@hirezstudios.com. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF ANY OF OUR SITES OR SERVICES
WILL SIGNIFY AND BE DEEMED TO CONSTITUTE YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF ANY CHANGES TO THIS
PRIVACY POLICY.
Privacy Statement
Hi-Rez respects the privacy of its users and recognizes the importance of protecting the information
collected about you. We have adopted a companywide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store,
and use the information you provide. This Privacy Policy applies both to persons who register or establish
an account with Hi-Rez and to casual users of our Sites and Services.
If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our Privacy Policy or use of your information,
please contact our legal department at legal@hirezstudios.com.
In addition, Hi-Rez owns several other domain names that link or point to the websites listed above, and
we will from time to time add new games and new websites that may or may not be listed above. Please
note that this Privacy Policy applies only to the websites maintained by Hi-Rez, and not to websites
maintained by third parties to which the websites listed above may link.
Third Party Web Sites
If you click on a link to a third party website, including, without limitation, any third party payment services or
other services offered through the Site or any advertisement or link to an online advertising company, you
will leave the Hi-Rez Site you are visiting and go to the website you selected. For example, you may be
required to establish a STEAM account with Valve Corporation to use our game(s), and you may be required
to provide credit card and other information to Valve Corporation and our other third party payment
processors when you purchase products or services from our Site or through our Service. Because we
cannot control the activities of third parties, including third party payment service providers and other service
providers, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and
we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as Hi-Rez. IF YOU
VISIT A THIRD PARTY WEBSITE THAT IS LINKED TO THE SITE, YOU SHOULD CONSULT THAT
WEBSITE’S PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE PROVIDING ANY PERSONAL OR OTHER INFORMATION. We
also encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request
services.
What is personal information and when does Hi-Rez collect it?
Personal information is information that is related to you, and may be used to contact you online or offline.
Hi-Rez collects personal information when you submit it to Hi-Rez through online and offline methods.
Online visitors typically submit information to Hi-Rez through (1) the purchase of goods or services through
the Site or Service, (2) use of our software or online services (including, without limitation, when you register
for an account with Hi-Rez), (3) participation in message boards and contests (including, without limitation,
in connection with registering and claiming prizes), (4) warranty registration, (5) customer support or
technical service requests, (6) player match-up or other online services, (7) registration for games or special
game-specific event participation, (8) marketing surveys and e-mail campaigns, (9) requests for services
from third party service providers on our websites, (10) surveys and newsletters, and (11) consumer
complaints. Hi-Rez may also collect personal information from you in-person or over the phone when you
register for, travel to, or attend an event or competition. Lastly, we may collect personal information that is
necessary to fulfil a legitimate interest, which will be described to you at the time of collection. Hi-Rez will
use this information for the purposes of which it was collected.
Personal information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail
address, phone number, mobile number, home address, birth date, credit card information, and other
personal information as defined under applicable law. We do not require this information to gain access to
the Site; however, you may not use certain features, products, or services (including, without limitation, the

Service) that require registration, or receive materials (e.g., newsletters), unless such information is
provided. You hereby consent to our collection and use of your personal information as outlined herein.
Other Information Collected
Certain activities will require you to create a username and password and provide other personal
information, such as your age, date of birth, gender, game, and other preferences. In addition, we may
collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware,
software, platform, media, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and connection, information about online activity
(e.g., feature usage), gameplay statistics and scores, user rankings, and click paths and other data that
you may provide in surveys or online profiles. In addition, we may combine demographic information with
personal information. Prize winners may also be required to provide Social Security or Social Identification
Numbers for tax purposes.
When you play our games, we may retrieve information about your hardware system, gameplay and how
our games are used, including, without limitation, your Internet Protocol Address, your gameplay
characteristics and patterns. We use this information to enable you to play our game(s) over the Internet.
We also use this information to better understand the behavior and preferences of our customers so that
we can improve our products and services.
If you log into your user account through social media sign-in services (e.g., Facebook Connect), you
provide Hi-Rez with permission to access certain information about you from that social networking site,
such as your Facebook User ID, user profile, friends list, and profile picture.
In addition to the information that we collect from you directly, we may also receive information about you
from other sources, including third parties, business partners, our affiliates, or publicly available sources.
Online Chat Rooms, Forums and Profiles
You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online message boards, chat rooms, forums,
or in creating user “profiles” when you play games on our Site or utilizing the Service. Information that you
disclose in message boards, chat rooms, forums, or in “profile” information is public information, and there
is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. Please see our Terms of Service and Use Agreement on this
point and for other guidelines about posting content on our websites.
Public Data
Your participation in tournaments or other online game events is conditional upon your agreement to us
collecting, using, storing, transmitting, and publicly displaying performance and statistical data (e.g., your
scores, rankings, and achievements) generated through your participation in the foregoing.
A Special Note About Children
Hi-Rez does not permit access to the Site or Service by children under the age of thirteen. If you are under
thirteen years of age, you should not access, or attempt to obtain access to, the Site or Services. Once a
child states that his or her age is under thirteen, we do not collect or store any personally identifiable
information such as name, address, or email address. Teenagers age thirteen or older, but who are under
the age of eighteen must have their parents or guardians review this Privacy Policy and should encourage
them to contact us if they would like to raise any concerns.
What about cookies and other technologies?
We may use cookies and other technologies to collect demographic information, personalize your
experience on our Site, and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded
to your computer to track movements and behavior within websites. Certain of our websites may use
cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. Also,
we may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. For example, certain
of our websites may use “cookies” or other methods to monitor website usage. We may collect information
on what games are played, how much time is spent playing the games, and which ads or links are clicked.
We may link cookie information to personal information.

Certain of our websites use an outside ad company to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies
received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and Hi-Rez does not have access to this
information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can
disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our
Site will not function properly if you do so.
Other technologies used in our websites include clear GIFs and IP address logging. Clear GIFs (i.e., web
bugs, beacons, or tags) are small graphic images placed on a webpage, web-based document, or in an e-
mail message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (e.g., only 1-by-1
pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, document, or e-mail message. We do not
use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. However, we may use clear GIFs to capture
statistical usage information for our webpages, features, or other elements on a webpage. We may correlate
this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on
our webpages.
Hi-Rez also maintains log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is
assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). In general, we only use log files to
monitor traffic on our websites, to report aggregate information to our advertisers and third party service
providers, and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of our Site; however, we may
block certain IP addresses or console IDs provided by our licensed hardware manufacturers. IP addresses
and console IDs may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Service and Use
Agreement.
What happens to the information provided?
The personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features, and
enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and contests and events of interest. We may send e-
mails that may contain information regarding third party products or services; however, this does not mean
that we have provided or traded your personal information to any party.
We may use survey information in marketing surveys to select and direct advertising that is more likely to
be of interest to a particular user of an account with Hi-Rez. This information may be transmitted to an ad
server owned by an advertising company to match account holders with ads that they are more likely to be
interested in. However, we do not disclose any account holder’s personal information to our advertisers
without the holder’s consent. Participation in such surveys is entirely optional. We may share aggregate
consumer data (which does not contain personally identifying information) with the advertising companies
or with any other third party, and we may use such information for any legitimate business purpose in our
sole discretion.
We may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can
consistently improve our websites to better meet our visitors’ and users’ needs. In addition, we may use
your personal information to enforce legal rights and comply with the law, or to comply with an order from
a judicial or government entity or other competent authority, or when we have reason to believe that a
disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property,
operations, users, or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage. Finally, we may also
disclose personal information to law enforcement, or the appropriate judicial or civil authorities.
Sharing of information held?
In addition to the specific situations discussed elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we disclose personal
information in the following situations:
     • Affiliates and Acquisitions. We may share your personal information with our corporate affiliates
          (e.g., parent company, sister companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under
          common control). In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of
          bankruptcy, visitor and user information (including, without limitation, personal information)
          maintained by Hi-Rez may be transferred to its successors or assigns.
     • Other Disclosures with Your Consent. We may ask if you would like us to share your personal
          information with other unaffiliated third parties who are not described elsewhere in this Privacy
          Policy.

     •   Other Disclosures without Your Consent. We may disclose personal information in response to
         subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, or in connection with any legal process, or to comply with
         relevant laws. We may also share your personal information in order to establish or exercise our
         rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible
         illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies, or for
         any other proper purpose to law enforcement, or the appropriate judicial or civil authorities.
     •   Partner Promotion. Users who register for an account with Hi-Rez may register for other third
         party partners from our Site, or link a Hi-Rez account to an account with such third party partners,
         from time to time. If you opt-in to any of these services, we may collect additional information
         including, without limitation, information requested by a third party, and pass this information,
         together with all other registration information (including, without limitation, personal information),
         to that third party partner. Use of your personal information by a third party partner will be governed
         by that third party provider’s privacy policy and terms of service. We may also retain any additional
         information collected for use in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Participation in
         these other related services is optional and is not required to access our Site, though some
         functionality may depend upon it.
     •   Service Providers. We may share your personal information with service providers. Among other
         things service providers may help us to administer our website, conduct surveys, provide technical
         support, assist in the fulfillment of orders, and for other legitimate purposes permitted by applicable
         law.
Sharing with Social Networking Sites
The Site may offer you the ability to share your personal information through a social networking site (e.g.,
Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn), using such social networking site’s integrated tools (e.g., Facebook “Like”
button, or Twitter “Tweet” button). The use of such integrated tools enables you to share personal
information about yourself with other individuals or the public, depending on the settings that you have
established with such social networking site. Additionally, by making personal information available on the
Site, you “opt in” to allow Hi-Rez to provide such personal information to a social networking site without
your further consent. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and use in
connection with such social networking site or a site’s integrated tools, please visit the privacy policies of
the entities that provide these social networking sites.
Where is the information held?
Currently, Hi-Rez maintains and stores your personal information on servers located within the United
States. This may not apply to Hi-Rez’s third party providers (including, without limitation, Valve Corporation
and our third party payment processors). In the event that Hi-Rez becomes a global organization, some of
the computer systems on which Hi-Rez collects, stores, and uses the information it collects or receives may
be based outside the United States. Therefore, your personal information may be transferred to, used,
processed, or held by Hi-Rez in the United States and in other countries, including, without limitation,
countries both in and outside the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.
You hereby consent to such use, storage and transfer of your personal information.
Retention of Personal Information
Hi-Rez retains your personal information: (a) for so long as your account is active or as needed to provide
you with Services or to fulfill our contractual obligations; (b) as necessary to comply with our legal
obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements; and (c) for so long as is necessary for the
purposes for which we collected such personal information.
Opt-out Provision
When you register your account, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of receiving Hi-Rez
marketing communications, including event invitations, special offers, and newsletters.. If you choose to
have your name removed from our mailing list, you can do so by contacting our support desk at
<http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/> or email privacy@hirezstudios.com. You can also
change your settings for receiving marketing communications on your Hi-Rez Account page at any time.
Safeguarding Your Personal Information

We will only collect and use personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to the extent
deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will use reasonable
safeguards to preserve the security, integrity, accuracy, and privacy of the information you have provided.
In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer any personal
information will provide commercially reasonable protection of that information. We cannot, however,
ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Hi-Rez, and you do so at your own risk.
However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed,
altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, managerial, or other safeguards.
If Hi-Rez learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you
can take appropriate protective steps. Hi-Rez may post a notice on its Site if a security breach occurs.
Review and Correction of Your Information; Requests for Removal from Mailing Lists; and
Deactivating Your Account
If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by Hi-Rez is not correct, or
should you wish to have your account(s) deactivated or be removed from our mailing list, please contact
our      support      desk     at     <http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/>      or    email
privacy@hirezstudios.com describing, in reasonable detail, the nature of the request, problem, or concern.
We will then review, update, or remove information as appropriate within a commercially reasonable time
frame after receiving such notice from you. We may still retain your information in our electronic data or
other files, however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement(s) and/or policy(ies), and due to
technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity, and operation of our
websites.
Display Advertising
Hi-Rez uses the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting features of Google Analytics for
Display Advertising. You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google
Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Preference Manager, which is available at
<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>.
Hi-Rez encourages visitors to read about the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, which is available
at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.
Hi-Rez and Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third party cookies
together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to Hi-Rez websites. This means that
vendors, including Google, will display Hi-Rez promotional material on other websites you visit across the
Internet. Hi-Rez also analyzes aggregate information provided by Google Analytics to determine usage
trends, which allows us to improve our websites and make it easier for you to find what you need.
Notice to California Residents
Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with Hi-Rez or its
Affiliates may choose to opt out of Hi-Rez’s disclosure of personal information about them to third parties
for direct marketing purposes. As detailed in this Privacy Policy, our policy is not to disclose personal
information collected online to a third party for direct marketing purposes without your approval. If you
choose to opt-out at any time after granting approval, contact our support desk at
<http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/> or email privacy@hirezstudios.com or write to:
Account Management, Hi-Rez Studios, Inc., 3750 Brookside Parkway, Suite 200 Alpharetta, Georgia
30022.
Notice to Residents of the European Economic Area
In accordance with applicable laws, you may have the right to request access to, rectification, and erasure
of your personal information; restriction of processing of personal information; objecting to certain
processing of personal information; and the right to data portability. Where any processing of personal
information is solely dependent upon your consent, you have the right to withdraw such consent at any time
(For example, we suggest by using any unsubscribe link contained in an applicable marketing message, or
emailing us at <http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/> or email privacy@hirezstudios.com).
Where you believe that we have not processed your personal information in accordance with applicable

laws, you may lodge a complaint with the respective supervisory authority or data protection regulator. The
provision of personal information by you will be for contractual, marketing, or analytical purposes as referred
to in this Privacy Policy.
To exercise your rights under these provisions, please contact us at the contact details below. When we
receive your request, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. We may
withhold information where we are required by law to do so or the search for that information would require
disproportionate effort or have a disproportionate effect to, for example, the cost of providing the
information, the time it would take to retrieve the data, or how difficult it may be to obtain the information
requested.
Communications
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or any other privacy or security
issue, please contact us at:
Hi-Rez Studios
Attn: Legal Department
Email: legal@hirezstudios.com.
Or at:
Legal Department, Hi-Rez Studios, Inc., 3750 Brookside Parkway, Suite 200 Alpharetta, Georgia 30022
Effective as of May 25, 2018
